http://www.yessy.com/privacy.html

Buy Art Browse ArtYour OrdersBuyer FAQSell Art 14-Day Free TrialSeller FAQSign In Your Account Help0 Cart
Privacy Policy
Yessy respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use Yessy. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy").
1. COOKIES
Cookies are not a requirement in order to use Yessy, however, cookies will enhance your experience. Yessy uses cookies to remember your shopping cart, to remember your email address so that you can sign in faster, to keep you signed in, and various tasks related to Yessy. Yessy will not disclose cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Yessy will continue to function properly if you refuse cookies.
2. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
Yessy does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. Yessy collects personal information and information about your transactions when you use Yessy services, such as buying and selling art. When you register, Yessy asks for your email address. Additional information is requested when you buy and sell art, such as your name, address, phone number, and payment information. Once you register with Yessy and sign in, you are no longer anonymous to Yessy.
Yessy automatically receives and records information on the Yessy server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Yessy cookie information, and the page you request.
3. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE
Yessy does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies. Yessy may divulge aggregate information about users but will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. For example, Yessy may disclose how frequently the average Yessy user visits Yessy, or which sort of art is most popular. Please be aware, however, that Yessy will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or if Yessy believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
4. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY
Yessy limits access to personal information about you to employees who Yessy believes reasonably need to come into contact with that information in order to do their jobs.
Yessy has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. Your Yessy account information is password-protected. In certain areas, such as Checkout, Yessy uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
5. PREFERENCES
Yessy reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to Yessy, such as service announcements and administrative messages, which are considered part of Yessy membership, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
6. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
By using Yessy, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this policy and to the Terms of Service. Yessy may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy can always be found at: https://www.yessy.com/privacy.html.
7. QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS
Any questions or suggestions can be sent to Yessy as follows:
Email: support@yessy.com
Mail:
Yessy, Inc.
Re: Privacy Policy
151 Calle San Francisco
Suite 200 - PMB 5077
San Juan, PR 00901
For BuyersBrowse ArtYour OrdersBuyer FAQFor Sellers14-Day Free TrialSeller FAQSign InYessy Art GalleryContactAboutHelp
© Yessy, Inc.  •  Terms    •    Privacy    •    Affiliate Program
